Privacy Policy
==============

The Privacy Policy ("Policy"), effective September 17, 2020, tells you about Larson Texts’ privacy practices governing personal information we may collect when you visit our larsontexts.com website, and how we may use and share that information. Your prior activities on the site may have been governed by an earlier version of this Policy.

From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Policy. If our information practices do change materially, we will post the changes to our site and revise our Policy accordingly. In addition, if we have collected personally-identifying information from you, we will notify you and secure your consent before using your personal information in new ways.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
-------------------------------

### Personal Information:

We collect personal and contact information you choose to provide to us in connection with your voluntary inquiries through our Contact Us page.

### Other user information we collect:

In addition, for each visitor to our site, we automatically gather certain other potentially identifying information and store it in log files. This information includes (as applicable) browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, your operating system, date/time stamp, processor or device serial number, unique device identifier, and clickstream data. We collect and store this information on an individual basis and in aggregate, or combined, form.

### "Do Not Track" Signals.

We do not currently have the capability to recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals. We adhere to the standards set forth in this privacy policy.

### Cookies –

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited. We use secure session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. We use session cookies to record session information, such as which web pages a user has visited, and to track user activity on the site. These cookies are deleted when you close your web browser.

### Analytics –

To determine how many users visit our site, how often they visit the site, and to better understand the areas of greatest interest to our visitors, we use a tool called “Google Analytics” to compile this information for us. As a result of your visit to our site, Google may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of analytics tools with personally identifiable information. For more information about the analytics companies’ ability to use and share information about your visits to this site, see [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Advertising –

We do not use third-party ad networks, targeted advertising, or display ads on this site.

WHO OWNS THE DATA WE COLLECT?
-----------------------------

We make no claim of ownership of your personal information. We retain rights to all aggregate and depersonalized data created through your use of the site.

HOW DO WE USE AND SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?
---------------------------------------------------

We store and process your personal information to respond to any inquiries you may make through our Contact Us page.

We also use information we collect to analyze trends, to administer the site, and to track users’ movements around the site. We also use this information to improve the site and to make it more useful to visitors.

We do not share personal information we collect on this site with any unaffiliated third parties, except that we may share personal information where we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

It is possible that, at some time in the future, our company may be sold along with its assets, or may engage in business transactions in which customer information is one of the assets transferred. In such a case, the customer information which we have gathered may be one of the business assets we transfer.

HOW LONG DO WE KEEP THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?
-----------------------------------------------

We will retain your personal information in accordance with our continuing business need to service this relationship and as may be required by law. When it is no longer being used for these purposes, we will destroy personal information in our possession within a reasonable time.

SECURITY
--------

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, and to guard that information against loss, misuse, or alteration. Confidential and sensitive information is encrypted throughout.

Please note, however, that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we use commercially-reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES
--------------------------

This Policy applies only to information collected by this site. From time to time, this site may link you to other sites (“Linked Sites”) that are not owned by us (for example, if you wish to inquire about an employment opportunity). We do not control the collection or use of any information, including personal information, that occurs during your visit to the Linked Sites. Further, we make no representations about the privacy policies or practices of the Linked Sites, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices.

Be careful of disclosing any of your personally identifiable information when leaving our site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every site that collects personally identifiable information.

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
------------------

This site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is a child under the age of 13.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
-------------------------

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, users who are California residents can request certain information about the sharing of their own personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the past year. The information which you have a right to receive includes the categories of personal information disclosed by us for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year and the names of the companies that received such information. You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format, and the information will not be specific to you individually.

Pursuant to the California Consumer Protection Act, (“CCPA”), California residents have additional rights with respect to their personal information. Please see our [CCPA Notice](https://www.larsontexts.com/privacy-policy/ccpa/) for details.

California residents can request this disclosure by sending a request to us using the contact information provided below. Please provide sufficient information to allow us to identify you in our records.

QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY
----------------------------------

If you have any questions about the Policy or our privacy practices, you may contact:

Larson Texts  
1762 Norcross Road  
Erie, PA 16510  
(877) 552-7766  

© 2024 Larson Texts, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
